ROSS GORDON

FRONT END DEVELOPER ♥ RICHMOND, VA, UNITED STATES (314) 762-7819

□ DETAILS □

Richmond, VA
United States
(314) 762-7819
rossagordonstl@gmail.com

- LINKS -

Linkedin

GitHub

□ SKILLS □

HTML & CSS

Bootstrap

JavaScript

React

React Native

Node.js

Express

MongoDB

Git/Git Hub

VS Code

PROFILE

Front-End Developer. Apple Genius. Drummer. Traveler. Born in St. Louis, Missouri. Living in Richmond, Virginia.

Full Stack + Mobile Bootcamp Graduate - JavaScript | React | HTML5 | CSS3 | Bootstrap | React Native | MongoDB | Node.js | Git/GitHub

5 years experience in IT support. Strong understanding of software troubleshooting and hardware repairs.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Genius at Apple, Inc., Richmond, Virginia, United States

March 2020 — Present

Certified Mac Repair Technician Certified in macOS troubleshooting

AppleCare- At Home Advisor at Apple, Inc., Richmond, VA, United States

April 2020 — June 2020

Supported AppleCare iOS Tier 1 during COVID-19 retail store closures.

Technical Expert at Apple, Inc., Richmond, Virginia

August 2017 — March 2020

Certified iOS Technician- Hardware repairs and software troubleshooting

Technical Specialist at Apple, Inc., Richmond, Virginia, United States

December 2017 — July 2018

Certified iOS technician

Specialist at Apple, Inc., Richmond, Virginia, United States

August 2017 — December 2017

Determined needs of customer for both personal and professional use. Knowledgeable on all Apple hardware.

Shipping/Logistics Lead at Kaldis Coffee Roasting Company, St. Louis

August 2013 — July 2016

Drum Instructor at Self Employed , St. Louis

October 2014 — July 2016

15 years of drumming experience. Former fulll-time touring musician. Self-Employed Drum Teacher. Traveled to the homes of clients for weekly one-hour lessons.

EDUCATION

Full-Stack + Mobile Bootcamp Bootstrap, React, React Native, NodeJS, MongoDB, Git/GitHub, Nucamp Coding Bootcamp

November 2021 — April 2022

Web Development Fundamentals HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Nucamp Coding Bootcamp January 2021 — December 2021

General Studies General Studies, J Sargeant Reynolds Community College

January 2018 — December 2020

★ CERTIFICATIONS

Nucamp- Full Stack Web Development + Mobile Coding Bootcamp

November 2021 — April 2022

Successfully completed Nucamp's Full Stack + Mobile bootcamp. Over 22 weeks, I worked with my instructor and cohort to learn the following technologies:

Bootstrap | React | React Native | Node.js | Express | MongoDB

Nucamp Coding Bootcamp- Web Development Fundamentals

October 2021 — November 2022

Successfully completed a 4 week refresher course to prep for the Full Stack Bootcamp. During this 4 weeks, I learned the following technologies:

-HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript ES6, VS Code, Git/GitHub